O	L705	Acne excoriée des jeunes filles
N	L705	Acne excoriee des jeunes filles
O	M0888	Other juvenile arthritis, vertebrae
N	M0888	Other juvenile arthritis, other specified site
O	M1208	Chronic postrheumatic arthropathy [Jaccoud], vertebrae
N	M1208	Chronic postrheumatic arthropathy [Jaccoud], other specified site
O	M1228	Villonodular synovitis (pigmented), vertebrae
N	M1228	Villonodular synovitis (pigmented), other specified site
O	M1238	Palindromic rheumatism, vertebrae
N	M1238	Palindromic rheumatism, other specified site
O	M1258	Traumatic arthropathy, vertebrae
N	M1258	Traumatic arthropathy, other specified site
O	M1288	Other specific arthropathies, not elsewhere classified, vertebrae
N	M1288	Other specific arthropathies, not elsewhere classified, other specified site
O	M2508	Hemarthrosis, vertebrae
N	M2508	Hemarthrosis, other specified site
O	M2518	Fistula, vertebrae
N	M2518	Fistula, other specified site
D	M4717	Other spondylosis with myelopathy, lumbosacral region
D	M4718	Other spondylosis with myelopathy, sacral and sacrococcygeal region
O	M5001	Cervical disc disorder with myelopathy, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5001	Cervical disc disorder with myelopathy,  high cervical region
O	M5011	Cervical disc disorder with radiculopathy, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5011	Cervical disc disorder with radiculopathy,  high cervical region
O	M5021	Other cervical disc displacement, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5021	Other cervical disc displacement,  high cervical region
O	M5031	Other cervical disc degeneration, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5031	Other cervical disc degeneration,  high cervical region
O	M5081	Other cervical disc disorders, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5081	Other cervical disc disorders,  high cervical region
O	M5091	Cervical disc disorder, unspecified, occipito-atlanto-axial region
N	M5091	Cervical disc disorder, unspecified,  high cervical region
D	M5107	Intervertebral disc disorders with myelopathy, lumbosacral region
O	M8458XA	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, initial encounter for fracture
N	M8458XA	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, initial encounter for fracture
O	M8458XD	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, subsequent encounter for fracture with routine healing
N	M8458XD	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, subsequent encounter for fracture with routine healing
O	M8458XG	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, subsequent encounter for fracture with delayed healing
N	M8458XG	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, subsequent encounter for fracture with delayed healing
O	M8458XK	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, subsequent encounter for fracture with nonunion
N	M8458XK	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, subsequent encounter for fracture with nonunion
O	M8458XP	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, subsequent encounter for fracture with malunion
N	M8458XP	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, subsequent encounter for fracture with malunion
O	M8458XS	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, vertebrae, sequela
N	M8458XS	Pathological fracture in neoplastic disease, other specified site, sequela
O	T2056XA	Corrosion of first degree of cheek, initial encounter
N	T2056XA	Corrosion of first degree of forehead and cheek, initial encounter
O	T2056XD	Corrosion of first degree of cheek, subsequent encounter
N	T2056XD	Corrosion of first degree of forehead and cheek, subsequent encounter
O	T2056XS	Corrosion of first degree of cheek, sequela
N	T2056XS	Corrosion of first degree of forehead and cheek, sequela
D	T401X5A	Adverse effect of heroin, initial encounter
D	T401X5D	Adverse effect of heroin, subsequent encounter
D	T401X5S	Adverse effect of heroin, sequela
D	T408X5A	Adverse effect of lysergide [LSD], initial encounter
D	T408X5D	Adverse effect of lysergide [LSD], subsequent encounter
D	T408X5S	Adverse effect of lysergide [LSD], sequela
O	W9431XA	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during ascent or descent, initial encounter
N	W9431XA	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during descent, initial encounter
O	W9431XD	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during ascent or descent, subsequent encounter
N	W9431XD	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during descent, subsequent encounter
O	W9431XS	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during ascent or descent, sequela
N	W9431XS	Exposure to sudden change in air pressure in aircraft during descent, sequela
O	Y92002	Bathroom of unspecified non-institutional private) residence single-family (private) house as the place of occurrence of the external cause
N	Y92002	Bathroom of unspecified non-institutional (private) residence single-family (private) house as the place of occurrence of the external cause
